Guide to the California Oil Collection, 1905-1914
Department of Special Collections
California Oil Collection,
1905-1914
Special Collections M0078
Newsom, J. F.
250 items
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions:
None.
Provenance:
Acquired from W. P. Hammond
SCOPE AND CONTENT
This collection consists of reports on oil producing districts in Kern County and Santa Maria, California; data on exports from California ports, prices, and production figures; maps of oil districts; and a report on M. J. and M. & M. Consolidated Co. of California.
CONTAINER LIST
- J. F. Newsom. Report on the Sunset-Midway Oil District, Kern County, CA, 1910., Text (Box 1, Folder 1)
- J. F. Newsom. Report on the Sunset-Midway Oil District, Kern County, CA, 1910., Maps (Box 1, Folder 2)
- J. F. Newsom. "Complete Oil Dope" (Box 1, Folder 3)
- J. F. Newsom. Oil data (production, prices, etc.) Sunset and Midway oil districts, 1908-1910 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- J. F. Newsom. Oil data (production, prices, etc.) Sunset and Midway oil districts, 1908-1910 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Report on the possibilities of W. P. Hammon's Bill tract, Santa Maria district, CA, 1914;also Newsom's evaluation of the district, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous data on California oil production, price and export figures, 1908-1910 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Santa Maria fields. Oilport plant of the Refining and Producing Oil Company (Box 2, Folder 5)
- M. J. and M. & M. Consolidated Company of California, 1911-1913 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Exports from San Francisco, 1905-1912,from Southern California ports, 1913-1914,and from San Francisco to Hawaii and Alaska, 1908-1914 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Santa Maria oil fields production (Box 2, Folder 8)